{
    "id": "00f0cc3ebadd4393921ec5ca1536d437",
    "title": "Infinitives and gerunds",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b10b4c70067e40f0982a86d46c4ec538",
            "title": "Infinitives And Gerunds",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He is addicted ………………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to gambling",
                        "to gamble",
                        "gambling"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am interested ……………………….. to cook.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in learning",
                        "to learn"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Several top designers assisted …………………..  the park.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to create",
                        "in creating"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is averse ………………….. cards.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to play",
                        "to playing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I do not believe …………………… children.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to pamper",
                        "in pampering",
                        "to pampering"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is bent ……………………… trouble.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on creating",
                        "to create"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have hardly any chance ……………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to succeed",
                        "of succeeding"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is confident ……………………. the first prize.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to win",
                        "of winning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is desirous ………………………. his grandparents.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to meet",
                        "of meeting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Hereafter he is disqualified ……………………. any government post",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to hold",
                        "for holding"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}